Guide to the Stanford University, Academic Secretary, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Academic Secretary, records
1945-1968
SC0067
Stanford University. Academic Secretary.
3.5 Linear feet
Records of Academic Secretary H. Donald Winbigler, including correspondence, minutes, notes, reports relating to the Student Affairs and Services Committee (1947-1966), the Union Board of Governors (1945-1966), the Western College Association (1954-1968) and the Western Personnel Institute (1956-1964). Includes correspondence and architectural plans for Tresidder Memorial Union and correspondence regarding accreditation procedures and reports.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfer, Academic Secretary's Office, 1969.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Records of Academic Secretary H. Donald Winbigler, including correspondence, minutes, notes, reports relating to the Student Affairs and Services Committee (1947-1966), the Union Board of Governors (1945-1966), the Western College Association (1954-1968) and the Western Personnel Institute (1956-1964). Includes correspondence and architectural plans for Tresidder Memorial Union and correspondence regarding accreditation procedures and reports.
Access Terms
Stanford University. Academic Secretary.; Stanford University. Student Affairs and Services Committee.; Stanford University. Tresidder Memorial Union. Board of Governors.; Stanford University. Tresidder Memorial Union.; Stanford University. Western Personnel Institute.; Architectural drawings.; Minutes.; Notes.; Reports.; Universities and colleges--Accreditation.
Collection Contents
- Records
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, January 1947-December 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, February 1962-March 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, April 1963-May 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, June 1963-October 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, November 1963-March 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, April 1964-December 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, January 1965-September 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, October 1965-November 1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, December 1965-February 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, March 1966-June 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Student Affairs and Services Committee, September 1966-June 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Union Board, 1945-1953 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Union Board, 1954-1959 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Union Board, 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Union Board, January - May 1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Union Board, September 1962 - December 1963 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Union Board, January 1964 - February 1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Union Board, March 1965 - December 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Union Board, January - May 1966 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Union Board - Activities Subcommittee, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Western College Association, 1954-1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Western College Association (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Western College Association, 1956-1962 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Western College Association, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Western College Association, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Western College Association, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Western College Association, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Western Personnel Institute, 1945-1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Western Personnel Institute, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Western Personnel Institute, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Western Personnel Institute, July - December, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Western Personnel Institute, 1961-1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Western Personnel Institute, January 1963 - June 1964 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - BOXES MARKED SC 067a:
    - Administrative residence committee (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - General Studies, 1960-1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Admissions (Undergraduate), 1953-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Vanderbilt Foundation, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Committee on Medical Admissions, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - General Studies - overseas general, 1957-1961 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - General Studies - overseas general, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - General Studies - overseas general, 1963-1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - General Studies - overseas general, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)